<item>
<title>Most Evil</title>
<meta>
<content>movie</content>
<imdb></imdb>
<title>Most Evil</title>
<year></year>
<summary>Most Evil is an American forensics television program on Investigation Discovery presented by forensic psychiatrist Michael Stone of Columbia University. On the show, Stone rates murderers on a scale of evil that Stone himself has developed. The show features profiles on various murderers, serial killers, mass murderers and psychopaths</summary>

</meta>
<link>
<sublink>https://weshare.me/5faaf1e873077f47/MOST_EVIL_PART_1.mp4(Part 1 of 3)</sublink>
<sublink>https://weshare.me/a4b66c44921328b7/MOST_EVIL_DISC2.mp4(Part 2 of 3)</sublink>
<sublink>https://weshare.me/4b34b5f04e4e1c0f/MOST_EVIL_DISC3.mp4(Part 3 of 3)</sublink>
<sublink>search</sublink>
<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
</link>
        
<thumbnail>https://www.dvdplanetstore.pk/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/fdFczQICrXIFLaZjvQSFKD92r3Q-453x666.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart></fanart>
</item>



<item>
<title>Rampage : Killing Without Reason</title>
<meta>
<content>movie</content>
<imdb></imdb>
<title>Rampage : Killing Without Reason</title>
<year></year>
<summary>A documentary program that caters to enthusiasts of true crime, this disturbing miniseries explores the facts belying the most bizarre, grotesque and grisly mass-slayings in modern history, in such contexts as religious cults, school massacres and workplace killings Rampage: Killing Without Reason video. Each chapter in the ten-part program focuses on one particular criminal; highlights include Charlie Manson, Timothy McVeigh, and Marshall Applewhite of the Heaven's Gate Cult Rampage: Killing Without Reason movie. Each chapter features rare and never-seen footage, analytical detail, and commentary by experts who turn up to discuss the reasoning behind these horrid events</summary>
    
</meta>
<link>
<sublink>https://weshare.me/84a7bb823ec49763/RAMPAGE_Part_1.mp4 (Part 1 of 2)</sublink>
<sublink>https://weshare.me/ff9fad3726a15db7/RAMPAGE_DISC_2.mp4 (Part 2 of 2)</sublink>
<sublink>search</sublink>
<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
</link>
        
<thumbnail>https://c9.cduniverse.ws/resized/9000x9000/movie/674/8127674.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart></fanart>
</item>


<item>
<title>American Gangster - The TV Show</title>
<meta>
<content>movie</content>
<imdb></imdb>
<title>American Gangster - The TV Show</title>
<year></year>
<summary>American Gangster is a documentary television series, which airs on BET. The show features some of black America's most infamous and powerful gangsters and is narrated by Ving Rhames</summary>
    
</meta>
<link>
<sublink>https://weshare.me/6398665b8900215b/American_Gangster_Disc1.mp4(Part 1 of 3)</sublink>
<sublink>https://weshare.me/41e06ea7eacd9496/AMERICAN_GANGSTER_disc2.mp4(Part 2 of 3)</sublink>
<sublink>https://weshare.me/eb925e73f20e4e7c/AMERICAN_GANGSTER_Disc3.mp4(Part 3 of 3)</sublink>
<sublink>search</sublink>
<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
</link>
        
<thumbnail>http://s.sidereel.com/tv_shows/50099/giant_2x/80655-1.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart></fanart>
</item>

<item>
          <title>Waco</title>
          <meta>
                  <content>tvshow</content>
                  <imdb>tt6040674</imdb>
                  <tvdb>337749</tvdb>
                  <tvshowtitle>Waco</tvshowtitle>
                  <year>2018</year>
                  <title>Waco</title>
                 
          </meta>
          <link>
            <sublink>https://rapidgator.net/file/7bdf54e7bfe426589db71f0980ffaafa/TwoDDL_waco.101.720.web-tbs.mkv.html(Episode 1 RD LINK)</sublink>
          	<sublink>https://weshare.me/58fc0cba14cb0b03/Waco.101-SVA.mkv(Episode 1)</sublink>
                  <sublink>search</sublink>
                  <sublink>searchsd</sublink>
          </link>
          
          <thumbnail>https://www.thetvdb.com/banners/_cache/posters/337749-2.jpg</thumbnail>
          <fanart>https://www.thetvdb.com/banners/fanart/original/337749-2.jpg</fanart>
  </item>


<item>
          <title>American Crime Story : The Assassination of Gianni Versace</title>
          <meta>
                  <content>tvshow</content>
                  <imdb>tt2788432</imdb>
                  <tvdb>289108</tvdb>
                  <tvshowtitle>American Crime Story : The Assassination of Gianni Versace</tvshowtitle>
                  <year>2018</year>
                  <title>American Crime Story : The Assassination of Gianni Versace</title>
                 
          </meta>
          <link>
  <sublink>https://rapidgator.net/file/4b2b12859d1bbac2e7a7bcae446dedeb/American.Crime.Story.S02E01.720p.HDTV.x264-AVS.mkv.html(Episode 1 RD)</sublink>
  <sublink>https://rapidgator.net/file/4dd1f2df80c9c0b5cb01c5141b84ca89/American.Crime.Story.S02E02.720p.HDTV.x264-AVS.mkv.html(Episode 2 RD)</sublink>
                  <sublink>search</sublink>
                  <sublink>searchsd</sublink>
          </link>
          
          <thumbnail>https://www.thetvdb.com/banners/posters/289108-14.jpg</thumbnail>
          <fanart>https://www.thetvdb.com/banners/fanart/original/289108-16.jpg</fanart>
  </item>
  
<item>
<title>Amanda Knox</title>
<link>https://weshare.me/df9757fb48d2cc6b/Amanda.Knox.2016.HDRip.AC3.2.0.x264-BDP.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTY5NjE4MTQyNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzg1NjEwMDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>American exchange student Amanda Knox is convicted and eventually acquitted for the 2007 death of another student in Italy.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>What Happened in Vegas</title>
<link>https://weshare.me/232ca268d81d4403/What.Happened.In.Vegas.2017.1080p.WEB_DL.x264_eSc.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDkwMzllODAtMGE1OS00YzI0LWEyZDQtYzIzZTdiNzY4NzE4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTMxODE3NzI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Ramsey Denison investigates a terrifying pattern of police corruption and discovers that behind the shimmering surface of Las Vegas lies a police department with individuals willing to go to any lengths to cover up crimes.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Charles Manson Superstar</title>
<link>https://weshare.me/d48b677b04b7eb4f/Charles_Manson_Superstar_REDUX_(2012)_(Complete_Film)_by_Filmow___Dailymotion.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://alchetron.com/cdn/Charles-Manson-Superstar-images-99117fae-8b3e-4a0d-b191-d88c4fe97b2.jpg?op=OPEN</thumbnail>
<summary>Charles Manson Superstar is a documentary film about Charles Manson, directed by Nikolas Schreck in 1989.[1][2][3] Most of the documentary (the entire interview) was filmed inside San Quentin Prison. Nikolas and Zeena Schreck narrated the segments while images were shown, and music played in the background</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Cocaine Godmother : The Griselda Blanco Story</title>
<link>https://weshare.me/ca5dbd1dd78a04f7/Cocaine.Godmother.The.Griselda.Blanco.Story.2018.HDTV.x264-CRiMSON.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTRhYjE4ZGMtZGY4MS00NjAzLTg0ZTItMGQ3NmZlMjYyNDAxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Cocaine Godmother is an American biographical crime-drama television film directed by Guillermo Navarro and written by David McKenna. The film stars Catherine Zeta-Jones as Griselda Blanco, who was known as the Cocaine Godmother.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Brigham City</title>
<meta>
<content>movie</content>
<imdb>tt0268200</imdb>
<title>Brigham City</title>
<year>2001</year>
    
</meta>
<link>
<sublink>https://weshare.me/1e709f774f5a6f47/Brigham_City.mp4</sublink>
<sublink>https://srv46.vidzi.tv/hls2/ozuqjq5wz42qedz7nj4r5szoallfhr6xmz6axmbpl6rhj5i6k5gqdbhhxiyq/index-v1-a1.m3u8</sublink>
<sublink>search</sublink>
<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
</link>
        
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTI0OTMzNDgyNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDQ0MTUyMQ@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTI3NDY2MDU5MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwNDkxODc5._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>




<item>
<title>Albert Fish : In Sin He Found Salvation</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/Albert.Fish.In.Sin.He.Found.Salvation.DOCU.DVDRip.XviD-RiTALiNl.2007.avi</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/oXiJWG5CZUuwQm1jSWuZkoqSE46.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Albert Fish, the horrific true story of elderly cannibal, sadomasochist, and serial killer, who lured children to their deaths in Depression-era New York City. Distorting biblical tales, Albert Fish takes the themes of pain, torture, atonement and suffering literally as he preys on victims to torture and sacrifice</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Carl Panzram: The Spirit of Hatred and Vengeance</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/CarlPanzram_xvid.avi</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/wDIE31N7uN2FuuviZDVVm6gGq1T.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>The true story of lifelong criminal and serial killer, Carl Panzram who wrote his autobiography for a jail guard in 1928. Carl Panzram was a lifelong prisoner and a hate-filled serial killer. Brutalized in and out of various U.S. state prisons during 20th century America, Panzram unleashed a rampage of revenge that resulted in over 20 murders and countless acts of violent sodomy. A single act of kindness, by prison guard Henry Lesser, sparked a friendship that eventually influenced Panzram to write his autobiography. In 1930, Panzram was hanged for killing a laundry foreman at Leavenworth prison</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Thin Blue Line</title>
<link>https://weshare.me/bd0a1141eec5ec3e/The.Thin.Blue.Line.1988.720p.WEB-DL.AAC2.0.H.264-ViGi.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/xFN3xPDzN4O7oIBmxnLIh8VROIw.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Errol Morris's unique documentary dramatically re-enacts the crime scene and investigation of a police officer's murder in Dallas</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Tales of The Grim Sleeper</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/HBO.Documentaries.Tales.of.the.Grim.sleeper.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/1ywSDHEQky7RwdCm7dxa6jnXOm4.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>When Lonnie Franklin Jr. was arrested in South Central Los Angeles in 2010 as the suspected murderer of a string of young black women, police hailed it as the culmination of 20 years of investigations. Four years later documentary filmmaker Nick Broomfield took his camera to the alleged killer’s neighborhood for another view</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Pig Farm</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/thepigfarm.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/6LaJkDcidOilvGWVFCvJFU9AEVf.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>This is the story about Robert Pickton, Canada's most prolific serial killer.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Slaughtered At The Murder Hotel</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/SlaughteredTheMurderHotel.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ZsMHY47fSM4/maxresdefault.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>A documentary about H.H. Holmes who was a famed serial killer in the mid 1800s. He had a whole murder castle built specifically for that purpose. He spent nearly a decade hiring and firing builders to add pieces to his house that included pipes for pumping gas into bedrooms, a room built specifically to suffocate people, and a murder basement where he would strip the skin from his victims.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bayou Blue</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/bayoublue.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/ncvEB2etwF8hVubenkKKcxODxXi.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>From 1997 to 2006, serial killer Ronald Dominique raped and killed twenty-three men in poverty- stricken Southeastern Louisiana. Difficulties in apprehending Dominique ranged from the underfunding of law enforcement to a lack of family advocacy for the victims, to the general distraction by other catastrophes such as Hurricane Katrina. Bayou Blue meditates on the decay of a community.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Jeffrey Dahmer Files</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/the.jeffrey.dahmer.files.2012.dvdrip.x264-wide.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/eIIPonlNZAhAAmcoa1deoHpIFJ7.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>An experimental documentary film that uses archival footage, interviews, and fictionalized scenarios to tell the story of the people around Jeffrey Dahmer during the summer of his arrest in 1991.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Long Island Serial Killer</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/People.Magazine.Investigates.S01E01.The.Long.Island.Serial.Killer.The.Lost.Girls.720p.ID.WEBRip.AAC2.0.x264-BTW_xvid.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>http://static.tvgcdn.net/feed/1/870/thumbs/116513870_1300x1733.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>2 part Episdode into the investigation of The Long Island Serial Killer</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Tobin, Portrait of a Serial killer</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/TobinPortraitofaserialkiller.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/514eB9ejZSL.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>As serial killer Peter Tobin awaits his third murder conviction, investigators from the British television series Real Crime look back at his twisted life. Deemed too dangerous to ever be released from prison, police believe they've only begun to count his victims. Tobin himself brags of killing up to 48 people. What is the truth behind this well-dressed killer, known as the charming psychopath?</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>The True Story Of The Dating Game Killer</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/The.True.Story.of.the.Dating.Game.Killer.2017.ID.WEB.h.264-SHRPY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://cdn.123gocdn.com/images/tt6294806/poster.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>A true crime story following the investigation and eventual capture of serial killer Rodney Alcala, who appeared on The Dating Game amid a string of grisly murders in the 1970’s.</summary>
</item>



<item>
<title>Serial Killer with Piers Morgan</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/serial.killer.with.piers.morgan.2017.hdtv.x264-plutonium.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://metrouk2.files.wordpress.com/2017/11/piers-serial-killers.png?w=748&h=419&crop=1</thumbnail>
<summary>Piers Morgan interviews Mark Riebe a convicted American murderer, who confessed numerous times to the kidnapping and killing 13 women along the Gulf Cost in Florida</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jodi Arias : An American Murder Mystery</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/Jodi.Arias-An.American.Murder.Mystery_xvid.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>http://static.movieflixter.to/images/210/9/9e/9e410a83-dcf6-8a33-499c-a9af41a0269c.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Jodi Arias: An American Murder Mystery: Sadomasochistic sex, obsession, and jealousy gone wrong create a deadly combination in the twisted tale of Jodi Arias: An American Murder Mystery which re-examines one of the most salacious and sensational crimes to rock the nation. In the latest installment of the record-breaking American Murder Mystery franchise, leading true-crime network Investigation Discovery (ID) delves into the explosive investigation and trial of Jodi Arias for the murder of Travis Alexander in a case that was almost too stunning to be believed. When 30-year-old Alexander is found brutally murdered in his Mesa, Arizona home, police are shocked – who would have wanted to harm the popular salesman with no known enemies? But soon, investigators receive a bizarre phone call that changes everything. The caller is Alexander's mysterious ex-girlfriend – Jodi Arias. What happens next is too shocking to be real – but, it is.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Menendez Murders Erik Tells All</title>
<link>https://weshare.me/307dae4a7b9b4f43/The.Menendez.Murders.Erik.Tells.All.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>http://www.gstatic.com/tv/thumb/tvbanners/14686347/p14686347_b_v8_aa.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>A&E Network's true crime documentary re-examines one of the most infamous murder cases in U.S. history through unparalleled personal access to one of the convicted killers. Erik Menendez recounts his tortured past and the brutal murder of his parents that he and older brother Lyle committed in 1989, for which both were sentenced to life in prison. The series includes extensive phone interviews with Erik as well as rare footage, never-before-seen photos, and new interviews with prosecutors, law enforcement, close family, friends and medical experts. Former Los Angeles Assistant District Attorney Christopher Darden, TV host Larry King, Erik's wife Tammi and trial reporter Linda Deutsch are among the interviewees.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Steven Avery : Innocent Or Guilty</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/investigation.discovery.steven.avery-innocent.or.guilty.720p.hdtv.x264-w4f.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://tvruckus.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/unnamed-1.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>This Investigation Discovery documentary seeks to provide a new look at the Avery case and features interviews with some of the key figures in his trial, including prosecutor Ken Kratz and Avery’s defence lawyer Jerry Buting. Is Steven Avery guilty of murder, or is he the victim of one of the country’s worst ever miscarriages of justice?</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>PBS Frontline : Waco The Inside Story</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/WacoTheInsideStory.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>http://www.pbs.org/wgbh/pages/frontline/waco/graphics/front3.jpeg</thumbnail>
<summary>Waco: The Inside Story. FRONTLINE investigates the April 1993 FBI siege of the Branch Davidian compound at Waco, Texas</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>48 Hours Special : All American Murder The Rise And Fall of Aaron Hernandez</title>
<link>https://weshare.me/9fca8bbf3a12daf8/48.Hours.Mystery.2018.01.20.All-American.Murder.The.Rise.and.Fall.of.Aaron.Hernandez.1080p.AMZN.WEB-DL.DDP5.1.H.264-NTb.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>http://assets.nydailynews.com/polopoly_fs/1.3073459.1492612552!/img/httpImage/image.jpg_gen/derivatives/landscape_1200/aaron-hernandez.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Aaron Hernandez seemed to have it all. He turned a hardscrabble childhood into superstar NFL dreams. In 2012 he was on one of the all-time best teams in the NFL and was armed with a new $40 million contract extension. But then it all fell apart when he was arrested for the 2013 murder of semi-pro linebacker Odin Lloyd in North Attleboro, Massachusetts. He was convicted of murdering Lloyd in 2015 and in April 2017, Hernandez committed suicide in a Massachusetts prison where he was serving a life sentence. He was 27.</summary>
</item>



<item>
<title>48 Hours special : Secrets of Waco</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/48.Hours.2017.12.29.Secrets.of.Waco.1080p.AMZN.WEB-DL.DDP2.0.H.264-NTb_xvid.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>http://wwwimage4.cbsstatic.com/thumbnails/videos/w443/CBS_Production_News_VMS/536/731/david_koresh_full.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>48 Hours special called Secrets of Waco, a retired Texas United Parcel Service driver is breaking his silence about how he “unwittingly delivered large boxes of military grade guns and ammunition” to David’s controversial congregation prior to the 51-day standoff between the church and FBI officials in 1993.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Truth and Lies : Waco</title>
<link>https://weshare.me/981c11836563bcf8/truth.and.lies.waco.2018.hdtv.x264-w4f.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>http://a.abcnews.com/images/US/171218_vod_waco2_16x9_992.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>He claimed 'God spoke through him.' Now, 25 years after the 51-day stand-off at David Koresh's Branch Davidian compound, new details and what survivors reveal.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>JonBenet : An American Murder Mystery</title>
<link>https://weshare.me/a4e484fee0980679/JonBenet-An_American_Murder_Mystery__xvid.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/81gv7NpdD6L._RI_.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>A three-part miniseries exploring the various theories surrounding the unsolved murder of JonBenet Ramsey</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dying to be Famous : The Versace Murders</title>
<link>http://uptobox.com/71rgty4xjau9</link>
<thumbnail>http://www.artribune.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/07/20091204160435_Gianni-Versace.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Investigation inside the 1997 murder of Fashion Designer Gianni Versace</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dateline : The Death of Gianni Versace</title>
<link>http://uptobox.com/fgapwc88qqh3</link>
<thumbnail>https://img.nbc.com/sites/nbcunbc/files/files/styles/640x360/public/images/2017/4/29/170424_3507317_The_Death_of_Gianni_Versace.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Gianni Versace’s longtime partner Antonio D’Amico speaks about the murder of the fashion icon. Versace’s murder came amid a months-long manhunt for Andrew Cunanan. Keith Morrison reports</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>How it really happened : The Gianni Versace Murder</title>
<link>http://uptobox.com/p4854udk4u97</link>
<thumbnail>http://i2.cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/170109153029-how-is-really-happened-card-super-tease.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Those closest to Versace -- and his killer Andrew Cunanan try to unravel the mystery. 'How it Really Happened with Hill Harper' </summary>
</item>



<item>
<title>Dahmer on Dahmer : A serial killer speaks</title>
<link>https://weshare.me/e1ade363411303b5/Dahmer.on.Dahmer.A.Serial.Killer.Speaks.2017.1080p.AMZN.WEB-DL.DDP5.1.H.264-NTb.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/1G4OxsXywHeqyWgoD0hT3yZhddv.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Two-and-a-half decades ago, a man from Milwaukee named Jeffrey Dahmer was tried and convicted of 17 gruesome murders that occurred between 1978 and 1991. Dahmer was convicted of luring young men into his home, where he then drugged, sexually violated, killed and finally consumed them. Investigative journalist Nancy Glass secured exclusive access and the first televised interview with the famous serial killer. Dahmer on Dahmer: A Serial Killer Speaks' catapults viewers into Jeffrey Dahmer's psyche, providing a unique look at the life of a serial killer that shook the nation</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dateline : The Summer of Manson</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/Dateline.2017.08.04.The.Summer.of.Manson.1080p.WEB-DL.AAC2.0.x264-BTW.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://media3.s-nbcnews.com/j/msnbc/components/video/201708/manson_2_promo_friday_10-9c.nbcnews-ux-1080-600.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>An in depth look of that fateful summer night in 1969 when Charles Manson and his followers embarked on a 2 day killing spree</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>MSNBC : Will you kill for me Manson and his followers</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/will.you.kill.for.me.charles.manson.and.his.followers.2008.pdtv.x264-w4f.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://peopledotcom.files.wordpress.com/2017/03/charles-manson-2000.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>What drove the notorious “Manson family” together? MSNBC investigates the inner workings of the cult, what led them to kill, and the murders that would mark the end of the ‘60s peaceful era</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Manson Speaks : Inside the mind of a madman </title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/Manson.Speaks.Inside.The.Mind.Of.A.Madman.Part.1.480p.x264-mSD_xvid.avi</link>
<thumbnail>http://www.gstatic.com/tv/thumb/tvbanners/14853740/p14853740_b_v8_aa.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>The two-part special "Manson Speaks: Inside the Mind of a Madman" presents a new theory on Manson’s motives that does not align with the “Helter Skelter” theory he was prosecuted under; brings forth eye witnesses who are speaking publicly about Manson for the first time; and makes contact with the only convicted Manson Family killer who is currently out of prison and living under a pseudonym.The special also examines 26 hours of exclusive never-before-broadcast phone conversations with Manson that may change the scope of his crimes, almost five decades later</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Son of Sam : The Hunt for a Killer</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/son.of.sam-the.hunt.for.a.killer.2017.1080p.web.h264-edhd_xvid.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>http://www.tvweeklynow.com/images/9073/RIcksPix/Press%20Images%20Oct16/1-3.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>In the late 1970s, David Berkowitz plays a cat and mouse game with the NYPD. Interviews and archive footage explore the twist and turns of the investigation into the 44 caliber killer</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Evil Kin : The Bloody Benders (Rare episode)</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/Evil.Kin.S02E02.The.Bloody.Benders.720p.HDTV.x264-TERRA_xvid.avi</link>
<thumbnail>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-7NVCzUQjAbY/Ua3axn3hCvI/AAAAAAAABtA/ty20h3DfhVU/s320/bendersMarker.png</thumbnail>
<summary>A look at the most murderous family in American history The Benders</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Alcatraz : The search for the truth</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/Alcatraz-The.Search.for.the.Truth.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/qgCiMDuZcsMlr2RYBMWbYNxtBJX.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>More than 50 years after three men broke out of the world's toughest penitentiary, HISTORY's 'ALCATRAZ: SEARCH FOR THE TRUTH' uncovers new leads and exclusive family secrets that may solve this country's most notorious cold case</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>American Experience : Bonnie and Clyde</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/American.Experience.S28E01.Bonnie.and.Clyde.1080p.PBS.WEBRip.AAC2.0.x264-BTW_xvid.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/hcwEM36Nozk/maxresdefault.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>In the spring of 1934, throngs of onlookers flocked to two Dallas funeral homes hoping to catch a last glimpse of the famous outlaws Clyde Barrow and Bonnie Parker. For over two years, the country had been transfixed by their illicit romance and a violent crime spree that left a trail of dead bodies in its wake. Though their exploits were romanticized, Bonnie and Clyde and their Barrow Gang were believed responsible for at least 13 murders and numerous robberies and kidnappings. And while they were just small-time criminals compared to more well-known gangsters who were the centerpieces of J. Edgar Hoover's most wanted list, they held the attention of many Americans. In the years since their deaths, dozens of movies, documentaries and television series have been made glamorizing the lives and deaths of Bonnie and Clyde.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Banned in America Movies</title>
<meta>
<content>movie</content>
<imdb></imdb>
<title>Banned in America Movies</title>
<year></year>
<summary>"Banned In America" shows video clips of the darkest elements of human nature, society, and life; the very things that bring fear and disgust into our collective existences. Whether it be live executions, live suicides, or miscellaneous forms of evil, "America" shows us that a sinister world of death lies right outside our door, just waiting for our number to be called</summary>
    
</meta>
<link>
<sublink>>http://mookdog.tech/Bannedinamerica.mp4(Banned in America)</sublink>
<sublink>http://mookdog.tech/bannedinamerica2.mp4(Banned in America II)</sublink>
<sublink>http://mookdog.tech/bannedinamerica3.mp4(Banned in America III)</sublink>
<sublink>http://mookdog.tech/bannedinamericaIV.mp4(Banned in America IV)</sublink>
</link>
        
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/dJEb8GxsPbPwpgAZlieCxlC9C47.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart></fanart>
</item>
