<item>
<title>Broad Street Bullies</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IJgMQDkyJH0</link>
<thumbnail>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/c/cd/Broad_Street_Bullies_intro.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Broad Street Bullies is a 2010 documentary film produced and directed by veteran documentary filmmaker George Roy for HBO Sports. It chronicles the National Hockey League's (NHL) Philadelphia Flyers from their beginnings as an expansion team in 1967, to their back-to-back Stanley Cup championships (1974, 1975), and three straight Finals appearances (1974–76).
The film includes clips and photos from the era, along with interviews with players, writers, broadcasters, and other individuals involved with the Flyers and/or NHL hockey during that period. It is narrated by Liev Schreiber.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Complete History of the Philadelphia Eagles</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bVaekN_ha-I&t=613s</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51PKMHNKSBL._SX342_.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>This set is a complete history of one of the NFL's oldest franchises, beginning with the Eagles' founding in 1933 by the legendary Bert Bell through the team's loss in last year's NFC Championship game. Along the way we'll relive some of the most memorable -and infamous - moments in team history. They've won three National Football League championships, appeared in one Super Bowl and produced legendary sports figures such as Steve Van Buren, Chuck Bednarik, Norm Van Brocklin, Tommy McDonald, Dick Vermeil, Randall Cunningham, Reggie White and Donovan McNabb. They've called five stadiums "home," including Veterans Stadium with the 700-level that's reached folkloric proportions. Go behind the scenes and out on the field with unparalleled access to sidelines and rousing talks inside the huddles with the players that proudly wear midnight green</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Michael Jordan : The Legend of The Greatest</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=42OzpZB0bqA&t=169s</link>
<thumbnail>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-CfodiE6qjKU/UQmp2sNdMLI/AAAAAAAAGlw/g5XKXOs89Pc/s1600/111.png</thumbnail>
<summary>4 hours of Michael Jordan, seemingly every offensive play in his career...I know its not but if seems like it..and his college career...Also passes and blocks and just a lot of ridiculous stuff....To hell with the 3 point shooters..this man may be the greatest shooter also in NBA history</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Americas Game The 1992 Dallas Cowboys</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uE1Luzevrrs</link>
<thumbnail>http://www.sportshdwallpapers.com/download/nfl-dallas-cowboys-logo-grey-on_1920x1200_332-wide.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>The Story of The 1992 Dallas Cowboys</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Complete History of The Denver Broncos</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ocde-LfElis</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/515t78cmxOL.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>the Complete History of the Denver Broncos. NFL Films takes you inside the Broncos with ELWAY, ALZADO, SHANAHAN, and many more</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Complete History of The Chicago Bears</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Uz5WIbqiIoA</link>
<thumbnail>http://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w500/7T3cmA3iKspJWu1NQipTfSreZeH.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>The Chicago Bears are one of the oldest and most storied franchises in the history of the National Football League. This two-disc set attempts to document the rich history of the club. In addition to lots of game footage, the disc includes the NFL films documentary on their Super Bowl XX win, a complete devastation of the New England Patriots. The game footage is presented in a standard full-frame transfer that preserves the original broadcast aspect ratio of 1.33:1.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Forever Hardcore ECW Wrestling</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uypCYi8KP8I</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjcyZDNlZjAtNTZhMC00Y2QxLTk5NDUtZWRjZTU5YzhmZWVkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjgxMTkzOQ@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>They revolutionized professional wrestling forever. A group of misfits, outcasts, and renegades led by a fearless visionary that ushered in a new era of professional wrestling from a dive bingo hall in south Philadelphia. Now, you will finally get the story from the mouths of the hardcore icons that lived it. FOREVER HARDCORE recounts the amazing story of how Tod Gordon's Eastern Championship Wrestling got hardcore and went on to impact the wrestling business forever. FOREVER HARDCORE takes you on an unsanitized journey through the highs and lows of a group of athletes that were never supposed to make it, and their reflections of why they will always be FOREVER HARDCORE</summary>
</item>
