
<plugin>
<title>[COLOR gold]To watch the Faces of Death YOU MUST be signed in to the youtube addon to prove your age. Otherwise it wont work[/COLOR]</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail></thumbnail>
</plugin>

<plugin>
<title>[COLOR gold]I have included the youtube addon in my repository http://repo.mookdog.tech[/COLOR]</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail></thumbnail>
</plugin>


<plugin>
<title>[COLOR gold]Some movies and shows are direct links from my own hosting server[/COLOR]</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail></thumbnail>
</plugin>



<item>
<title>Summer Camp Nightmare</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vo33mjBebPI</link>
<thumbnail>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/1/1e/Poster_of_the_movie_Summer_Camp_Nightmare.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>At Camp North Pines for Boys, the campers, led by the charismatic Franklin Reilly, stage a revolt against the strick owner, Mr. Warren, and lock him and the rest of the councelers up and take over the camp for themselves. But the revol soon spirals out of control as the boys also lead a takeover of the nearby girls camp as well. Then, Mr. Warren is accidently killed trying to escape. And, soon friction happens between the two boys and girls camps, which only one camper, a certain Donald Poultry, tries to get the word out and unseat Franklin as the leader</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Executioners Song - The Gary Gilmore story</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oD_wxyTHJ2I</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/wqvu3Gkqr52altilnFFF6Occ4aX.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>In this fact-based film, Gary Gilmore, an Indiana man who just finished serving a lengthy stay in prison, tries to start anew by moving to Utah. Before long, Gary begins an ill-advised romance with the troubled Nicole Baker, a teenage single mother. As their relationship quickly deteriorates, Gary goes on a murderous rampage, leaving two dead. During his trial, he demands capital punishment; a media circus ensues and outsiders look to profit from his story</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Adolf Hitler The Greatest Story never told (Over 6 hours)</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-FdGOkaJbjg</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/7ePDCY9RANdqNA1256N5WJ2ZyxW.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Far outside what's normally taught as "history", this 6-hour documentary attempts to explain what's normally glossed over - Germany's actions prior to WWII, Hitler's popularity, the support of the Nazis by the Germans, the basis for hardline Nazi stances against Jews, and why Nazism was such a danger to the established world powers. It chronicles the German WWI defeat, communist attempts to take over Germany; hyperinflation during the Weimar Republic, widespread unemployment and misery that served as the foundation of Nazi principles, and Hitler’s amazing rise to power. It also reveals a personal side of Hitler: his family background, his artwork and struggles, and what motivated him to pursue a career in politics. While open to criticism for being "pro-Nazi" in its perspectives, the documentary does present many factual foundations for those perspectives, highlighting an endless list of hypocrisies and double-standards imposed on Germany in the years before, during, and after WWII</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Serial Killers : The real life Hanibal Lecters</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mNnbMvogG9g</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTUzMDA5NDMzOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzk2NzI5Mw@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>This documentary examines a selection of real life serial killers and compares them to the fictional Hannibal Lecter</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Serial Killers : Murder, No Apparent Motive (1984 rare documentary)</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZzxTgn0BWpM</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BM2Y5NmMxYWMtZWUzNi00Y2RmLThhZWEtYjExNGI3ZGY2ZmU1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjkxODI3MTY@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,559,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Documentary about serial killers and FBI Behavioral Sciences Profilers. Interviews with Ed Kemper and Ted Bundy as well as crime victims and law enforcement officials. Includes some Dramatic Recreations.</summary>
</item>



<item>
<title>Serial Killers Still on the loose</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D60mt35Tczg</link>
<thumbnail>https://authorjenniferchase.files.wordpress.com/2011/04/serialkillers.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>The Documentary is about Serial Killers still on the loose throughout the US</summary>
</item>







<item>
<title>When Girls Kill Documentary</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xz5nVfY-cbA</link>
<thumbnail>http://www.flyermall.com/uploads/images/YOU%20TUBE%20FILES/KILLERS%208.JPG</thumbnail>
<summary>Documentary about numerous girls who are behind bars for murder</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mother's Day</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ptdFaWmnvcM</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/j58tLbbow4FXToIxgiKO8uUjW35.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Three girls discover that two men are willing to do anything to impress Mother and what impresses Mother is watching her sons commit acts of rape and murder. Now these women are prisoners and lowered to pawns in the game of checkers between two dim wits and their Maniac Mommy and the question becomes, can any of them escape, alive?</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Murder by Phone (Bells)</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3KmQoH9HMpw</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/rcEvVeTQINOX0WiwMFCO9iCnvbU.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>A disgruntled phone company employee develops a device whereby those answering a phone can be murdered, and it's up to Nat Bridger to stop the killer.</summary>
</item>



<item>
<title>Dahmer on Dahmer : A serial killer speaks</title>
<link>https://weshare.me/e1ade363411303b5/Dahmer.on.Dahmer.A.Serial.Killer.Speaks.2017.1080p.AMZN.WEB-DL.DDP5.1.H.264-NTb.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/1G4OxsXywHeqyWgoD0hT3yZhddv.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Two-and-a-half decades ago, a man from Milwaukee named Jeffrey Dahmer was tried and convicted of 17 gruesome murders that occurred between 1978 and 1991. Dahmer was convicted of luring young men into his home, where he then drugged, sexually violated, killed and finally consumed them. Investigative journalist Nancy Glass secured exclusive access and the first televised interview with the famous serial killer. Dahmer on Dahmer: A Serial Killer Speaks' catapults viewers into Jeffrey Dahmer's psyche, providing a unique look at the life of a serial killer that shook the nation</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dateline : The Summer of Manson</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/Dateline.2017.08.04.The.Summer.of.Manson.1080p.WEB-DL.AAC2.0.x264-BTW.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://media3.s-nbcnews.com/j/msnbc/components/video/201708/manson_2_promo_friday_10-9c.nbcnews-ux-1080-600.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>An in depth look of that fateful summer night in 1969 when Charles Manson and his followers embarked on a 2 day killing spree</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>MSNBC : Will you kill for me Manson and his followers</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/will.you.kill.for.me.charles.manson.and.his.followers.2008.pdtv.x264-w4f.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://peopledotcom.files.wordpress.com/2017/03/charles-manson-2000.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>What drove the notorious “Manson family” together? MSNBC investigates the inner workings of the cult, what led them to kill, and the murders that would mark the end of the ‘60s peaceful era</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Manson Speaks : Inside the mind of a madman </title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/Manson.Speaks.Inside.The.Mind.Of.A.Madman.Part.1.480p.x264-mSD_xvid.avi</link>
<thumbnail>http://www.gstatic.com/tv/thumb/tvbanners/14853740/p14853740_b_v8_aa.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>The two-part special "Manson Speaks: Inside the Mind of a Madman" presents a new theory on Manson’s motives that does not align with the “Helter Skelter” theory he was prosecuted under; brings forth eye witnesses who are speaking publicly about Manson for the first time; and makes contact with the only convicted Manson Family killer who is currently out of prison and living under a pseudonym.The special also examines 26 hours of exclusive never-before-broadcast phone conversations with Manson that may change the scope of his crimes, almost five decades later</summary>
</item>






<item>
<title>Evil Kin : The Bloody Benders (Rare episode)</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/Evil.Kin.S02E02.The.Bloody.Benders.720p.HDTV.x264-TERRA_xvid.avi</link>
<thumbnail>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-7NVCzUQjAbY/Ua3axn3hCvI/AAAAAAAABtA/ty20h3DfhVU/s320/bendersMarker.png</thumbnail>
<summary>A look at the most murderous family in American history The Benders</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Albert Fish : In Sin He Found Salvation</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/Albert.Fish.In.Sin.He.Found.Salvation.DOCU.DVDRip.XviD-RiTALiNl.2007.avi</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/oXiJWG5CZUuwQm1jSWuZkoqSE46.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Albert Fish, the horrific true story of elderly cannibal, sadomasochist, and serial killer, who lured children to their deaths in Depression-era New York City. Distorting biblical tales, Albert Fish takes the themes of pain, torture, atonement and suffering literally as he preys on victims to torture and sacrifice</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Green River Killer Gary Ridgway</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WYf2x4nti-Q</link>
<thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/WYf2x4nti-Q/maxresdefault.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Gary Ridgway also known as the Green River Killer, is an American serial killer. He was initially convicted of 48 separate murders and is presumed to be responsible for more than 90. As part of his plea bargain, an additional conviction was added, bringing the total number of convictions to 49, making him the most prolific serial killer in U.S. history according to confirmed murders.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Carl Panzram: The Spirit of Hatred and Vengeance</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/CarlPanzram_xvid.avi</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/wDIE31N7uN2FuuviZDVVm6gGq1T.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>The true story of lifelong criminal and serial killer, Carl Panzram who wrote his autobiography for a jail guard in 1928. Carl Panzram was a lifelong prisoner and a hate-filled serial killer. Brutalized in and out of various U.S. state prisons during 20th century America, Panzram unleashed a rampage of revenge that resulted in over 20 murders and countless acts of violent sodomy. A single act of kindness, by prison guard Henry Lesser, sparked a friendship that eventually influenced Panzram to write his autobiography. In 1930, Panzram was hanged for killing a laundry foreman at Leavenworth prison</summary>
</item>



<item>
<title>Going Postal</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UgUWOUuEDgk&t=120s</link>
<thumbnail>http://cdn0.documentaryheaven.com/wp-content/thumbnails/13724-370x278.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Going Postal is the tale of several school and workplace shootings which have been responsible for casting a large shadow over American society and generating fear since the 1980's. It is a modern phenomenon which has been coined "Going Postal", this film includes a large number of interviews with survivors, the families of those who died</summary>
</item>



<item>
<title>Aileen Wuornos : Selling of a serial killer</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oPD2hd6y_C8&t=49s</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/vQUCyCe28IesLhh3Q8ZpcbGsDMv.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Aileen Wuornos: The Selling of a Serial Killer (1993) is a documentary film about Aileen Wuornos, made by Nick Broomfield. It documents Broomfield's attempts to interview Wuornos, which involves a long process of mediation through her adopted mother Arlene Pralle and lawyer, Steve Glazer</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Aileen : Life and Death of a serial killer</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IsgVFplffl0&t=29s</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/6xK0WqH2fxGHXFFqOV0M96oTNC7.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>British documentarian Nick Broomfield creates a follow-up piece to his 1992 documentary of the serial killer Aileen Wuornos, a highway prostitute who was convicted of killing six men in Florida between 1989 and 1990. Interviewing an increasingly mentally unstable Wuornos, Broomfield captures the distorted mind of a murderer whom the state of Florida deems of sound mind -- and therefore fit to execute. Throughout the film, Broomfield includes footage of his testimony at Wuornos' trial</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Boneyard Leonard Lake and Charles Ng</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YBBDB6zAtxo</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/siIuXM3xiso2OwlaMgG5xmP50Uu.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>This is the true story of one of the most grisly crime scene investigations in the history of the United States. The grueling case - that began with a simple shoplifting arrest - unfolded clue by clue, until a shocking discovery rocked the nation: more than forty pounds of bones and five intact bodies buried on Charles Ng and Leonard Lakes' property. Each gruesome excavation confirmed that Ng and Lake were no ordinary serial killers. They were manipulative, sadistic, and had no mercy for their innocent victims. Walk alongside law enforcement, step by step, as they work to get justice for the slain</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>My Brother The Serial Killer</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8TIgjor9hLs</link>
<thumbnail>https://www.worldwidehippies.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/ap_glen_rogers_dm_121120_wg.jpeg</thumbnail>
<summary>This documentary chronicles the life of serial killer Glen Rogers through the eyes of his family. Glen traveled all over the US,killing along his travels. He even admits to being behind the killings of Nicole Brown Simpson and Ronald Goldman</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Stranger Beside Me</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hlrfHmYCxhI</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/lxxomWz6AACjM4jF6cKak7Ngtwu.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>While working at a Seattle clinic for women in the 1970s, Ann Rule becomes friends with Ted Bundy. Based on a book by Ann Rule</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Babysitter</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0WQgyelEuyw</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/c639nU9fOJaMakucyPPKTqTvHZp.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Overprotective mother Liz Benedict meets 18 year-old orphan Joanna Redwine and hires her as house help and live-in companion to rambunctious daughter Tara. Liz's husband Jeff isn't too thrilled with the arrangement, and his fears soon prove justified when Joanna begins to manipulate everyone and to slowly destroy the family. Meanwhile next-door neighbor Dr. Linquist investigates and discovers Joanna has a disturbing past</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>JFK : The Final Hours</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g7oI0HIs_S8</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/6i8dpdXDL52Ycjta8rZL4F2sEE.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Bill Paxton narrates this wonderful documentary taking a look at the final day in the life of President John F. Kennedy. The film pretty much traces his actions from the time he landed in Texas until his arrival in Dallas where he would of course be assassinated. The film starts off to a rather shocking, to me anyway, claim and that's the fact that Paxton himself was able to see Kennedy and have a photograph taken of himself in a crowd listening to the President give a speech the day before he was killed. Perhaps this here was known to fans of the actor but I personally never knew this but as the film plays out you see how those directly linked to the President on this day will never forget what happened and probably more than most people</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>JFK : 3 Shots That Changed America PART 1 of 2</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yg0f_QHNSUw</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/7aitPPYUdofTo8pj6RPMg88em4r.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>The film is an unnarrated collection of archived news and home movie footage shot as events unfolded, some of it rarely seen. Part one deals with the time from President Kennedy's arrival in Dallas on November 22, 1963 through the murder of Lee Harvey Oswald less than 48 hours later. Part two deals with the Warren Commission, its critics and those who suspect a conspiracy, the assassinations of Martin Luther King, Jr. and Robert F. Kennedy in 1968 and the turmoil that followed, and the continuing doubt about the assassinations and the effects this has had on American society</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>JFK : 3 Shots That Changed America PART 2 of 2</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1oE6NoGiAqE</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/7aitPPYUdofTo8pj6RPMg88em4r.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>The film is an unnarrated collection of archived news and home movie footage shot as events unfolded, some of it rarely seen. Part one deals with the time from President Kennedy's arrival in Dallas on November 22, 1963 through the murder of Lee Harvey Oswald less than 48 hours later. Part two deals with the Warren Commission, its critics and those who suspect a conspiracy, the assassinations of Martin Luther King, Jr. and Robert F. Kennedy in 1968 and the turmoil that followed, and the continuing doubt about the assassinations and the effects this has had on American society</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Who Was Lee Harvey Oswald</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x5MLlmwQ3fI&t=29s</link>
<thumbnail>http://static1.businessinsider.com/image/56c1daa76e97c627008b73ab-480/huluoswaldphotostill.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>PBS Frontline presents and in depth look into the life of Lee Harvey Oswald the assassin responsible for the death of JFK</summary>
</item>



<item>
<title>The Kidnapping of Elizabeth Smart</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E5aMT-nAuxA</link>
<thumbnail>https://www.earnthenecklace.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/Mitchell-2.jpg</thumbnail>
</summary>A behind the scenes look at what exactly happened to Elizabeth Smart on the day of her abduction</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Day John Lennon Died</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EjU7VMj94ss</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/3vISy9fxc6JVWlbbREBiVjvOjCU.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Reconstructing John’s last day in detail by way of radio and TV reports, the memories of people John knew and those he encountered before his assassination by Mark Chapman, relive one of the most momentous and tragic events in music history</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Certain kind of Death</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ErooOhzE268</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/oj23rwBgCZF4ULvYJNh7YNIc0Lx.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Unblinking and unsettling, this documentary lays bare a mysterious process that goes on all around us - what happens to people who die with no next of kin</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>NJ Shark Attacks of 1916</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6_4ROpsT1Wc&t=248s</link>
<thumbnail>https://news.nationalgeographic.com/content/dam/news/2015/07/02/sharkattack1916/02sharkattack1916.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>The incident Jaws was based on. A look at the 1916 shark attacks at the New Jersey shore</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>I survived 9/11</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u2o02upfA80</link>
<thumbnail>https://www.factslides.com/imgs/911-planes.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Interviews with the people who survived that fateful day Tuesday September 11th 2001 with archival footage of the incident</summary>
</item>

<plugin>
<title>Rare Horror movies</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/playlist/PLSeZ6qt37vqxTrOOedrgCRwWQVe2MMAqR/</link>
<thumbnail>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/e/e4/Rare_logo.png</thumbnail>
</plugin>


<item>
<title>Banned in America</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/Bannedinamerica.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/dJEb8GxsPbPwpgAZlieCxlC9C47.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>"Banned In America" shows video clips of the darkest elements of human nature, society, and life; the very things that bring fear and disgust into our collective existences. Whether it be live executions, live suicides, or miscellaneous forms of evil, "America" shows us that a sinister world of death lies right outside our door, just waiting for our number to be called</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Banned in America II</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/bannedinamerica2.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/ohSIvWBm9ZlgVadp4hosMLDHupV.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>This shocking, graphic release from the Banned in America franchise offers a disturbing collection of footage that is most definitely not appropriate for kids. The real, unedited scenes captured for the release include fatal car crashes, brutal acts of extreme, bloody violence, grotesque stunts, and more</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Banned in America III</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/bannedinamerica3.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/18aUGjOQrQfmx1hXeykpFxy9e44.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>This shocking, graphic release from the Banned in America franchise offers a disturbing collection of footage that is most definitely not appropriate for kids. The real, unedited scenes captured for the release include fatal car crashes, brutal acts of extreme, bloody violence, grotesque stunts, and more</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Banned in America IV</title>
<link>http://mookdog.tech/bannedinamericaIV.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/43HzuMQ3c9AXqSIKAUF3k3aYYJD.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>BANNED IN AMERICA IV gives you 4 times the action, 4 times the gore of any other shockumentary. We dare to show you the most brutal accidents, the most disturbing crime scenes, the most terrifying footage of ma, animal and machine gone wild. Do you have what it takes to watch?</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Banned From Television</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0FvLsXo-O9U</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/dT5Nj64XYQIesPQpYApFZv09JIl.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>A collection of uncensored video clips deemed too racy or violent for broadcast television</summary>
</item>



<item>
<title>Faces of Death</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p1m2xIfQyFA&t=3s</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/173PipLYSM829pdLHgYfpNNSMs3.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>A collection of death scenes, ranging from TV-material to home-made super-8 movies. The common factor is death by some means</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Faces of Death II</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aB0-oydpuV0</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/6O87VXAMLJjEW7SgWWkowIcMLmd.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>This movie continues in the same vein as F.O.D. 1 with short scenes of death related material. Mortuarys, accidents, police work are filmed by TV crews and home video cameras. Some of the material are most likely fake, some not as likely</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Faces of Death III</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oHqAF-aYHm0&t=28s</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/uCcTM3VDOqlwQGhyCsQ05dgOc6A.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>This third installment focuses largely on serial killers, with lengthy re-enactments of police investigations of bodies being found in a dumpster, and a staged courtroom sequence with Schwartz again making a cameo appearance as the serial killer on trial for raping and murdering a girl, allegedly captured on video. Schwartz has identified the girl allegedly killed in the video as his then girlfriend, who he claims was a willing participant</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Faces of Death IV</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ih89NYfQQSY&t=46s</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/wusQD7OxK3dA48mqqJBzRP2nNDF.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>Follows the same pattern of the other Faces of Death movies. In this one we see many staged and not so staged looking deaths ranging from bungee jumping accidents and magic tricks gone bad</summary>
</item>



